John James Audubon Papers 1821-1845 Mss.B.Au25
American Philosophical Society
- John James Audubon Papers, 1821-1845 (Box 1)
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1831 Oct. 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.140-142
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1831 Oct. 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.142-144
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1831 Oct. 30; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.145-146
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1831 Nov. 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.147-149
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1831 Nov. 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.149-151
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1831 Dec. 5; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.159-163
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1831 Dec. 8; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.164-168
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1831 Dec. 15?; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1832? Jan. 16; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.172-177
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1832 Feb. 1; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.177-180
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1832 Feb. 17; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.182-183
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1832 March 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.184-187
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1832 March 29; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.189-193
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1832 April 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.193-195
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1832 April 18; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1832 Nov. 6; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Feb. 1; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - From John Bachman to John James Audubon, 1833 Feb. 9; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Feb. 24; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.197-202
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 March 19; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 April 1; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.202-207
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 April 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.207-211
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Sept. 9; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p..240-247
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Sept. 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p..247-250
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Sept. 20; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p..251-255
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Sept. 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p. 255-261
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Oct. 11; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.261-263
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Nov. 4; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.263-267
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Nov. 5, Dec. 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Nov. 24; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Dec. 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.271-272
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1833 Dec. 21, 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.272-277
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 Jan. 1; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.1, p.277
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 Jan. 14; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.3-7
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 Feb. 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.8-10
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 March 9; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.10-13
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 March 12; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.13-15
  - To Richard Harlan, 1834 March 17; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 April 6, 8; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning,v.2, p.17-21
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 April 8; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 April 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.25-27
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834? May 6; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 May 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Baron Rothschild, 1834 June 19; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 July 4; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To John G. Children, 1834 Aug. 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1834 Sept. 5; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.33-38
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1834 Sept. 22; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.38-47
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1834 Oct. 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1834 Oct. 9; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1834 Dec. 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1836 Sept. 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.127-129
  - Journal leaves (Partial entries), 1836 Oct. 15, Nov. 8; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - List of materials for expedition, 1836 Oct. 27; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1836 Nov. 17; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To John James Abert, 1837 Jan. 10; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To John James Abert, 1837 Jan. 20; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1837 Feb. 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.139-144
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubo, 1837 March 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.153-154
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1837 July 8; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.165-167
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1837 Aug. 4; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.174
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1838 Nov. 8; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1839 Nov. 24; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.222-225
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Feb. 20; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Feb. 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.233-236
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Feb. 24; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Feb. 25; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Feb. 26; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Feb. 27; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1840 March 1; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.238-242
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 March 4; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.242-246
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 March 5; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 March 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.246-250
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 March 24; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 March 27; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.251-253
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 April 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.257-261
  - To Victor G. Audubon with postscript: Maria Martin, 1840 May 4; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.267-269
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 May 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.269-271
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 May 31; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 July 17; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 July 18; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.271-273
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 July 24; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.274-275
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 July 30; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
    Corning, v.2, p.275-278
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 1; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 5; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 6; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 9; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 14; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 20; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 21; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Aug. 22; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon with postscript: John W. Audubon, 1840 Nov. 1; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Nov. 8; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1840 Dec. 30; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Thomas McCulloch, Jr. (copy), 1840 Dec. 30; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon with postscript: John W. Audubon, 1841 Jan. 9; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1841 Jan. 30, 31; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon with postscript: John W. Audubon, 1841 Feb. 11; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1841 April 22; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To John Bachman with postscript: John W. Audubon, 1841 April 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Thomas McCulloch, Jr. (copy), 1841 Oct. 16; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Feb. 10; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 March 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 April 6; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 April 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 July 12; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 July 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 July 17; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 July 18; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 July 19; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 July 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1842 July 24; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 July 25; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Aug. 12; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Aug. 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Aug. 18; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Aug. 20; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Aug. 23; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1842 Aug. 24; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Aug. 25; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Sept. 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Oct. 3; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Oct. 5; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Oct. 6; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Oct. 6; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Oct. 9; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Oct. 10; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Dec. 11; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Dec. 15; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1842 Dec. 18; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 May 5; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 May 12; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 May 19; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 May 25; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 June 13; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 June 16; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 June 20; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 June 26; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 July 18; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 July 19; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 July 25; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 July 26; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 July 26; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 July 30; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 Aug. 3?; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 Aug. 7; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 Aug. 11; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 Aug. 14; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Victor G. Audubon, 1844 Sept. 6; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - From Thomas Brewster to Thomas McCulloch, Jr. (copy), 1845 Jan. 25; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851
  - To Mrs. Lucy Audubon, 1845 June 7?; Audubon, John James, 1785-1851